(Penny:)Hey.
Hi.
(Penny:)Hey, what's this?
(Leonard:)Listen, we did a stupid thing.
(Howard:)We went to a movie and
lied about it, but we feel bad
(Howard:)and want to make it up
to you.
(Leonard:)So, these are for you,
and if you're not too mad,
(Leonard:)we'd love to take
you guys to dinner.
WOLOWITZ: Yeah.
(Howard:)Anywhere you want.
Oh. Well,
(Bernadette:)thank you for being honest.
PENNY: Yeah. You know,
(Penny:)I want to be upset, but we did
(Penny:)kind of have fun
working on the prototype.
KOOTHRAPPALI: Don't forgive them!
Stay mad at them!
(Howard:)What is he doing
in there?
Busting you!
(Amy:)It's okay.
They apologized.
(Penny:)Yeah, it's fine.
(Raj:)Well this is kind
of anti-climactic.
(Leonard:)You know what
wasn't anti-climactic?
(Howard:)The end of the movie. Get this.
No spoilers! No spoilers!
(Penny:)And he's back
in the closet.
(Howard:)Ready for dinner?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Bernadette:)Should we invite Raj?
KOOTHRAPPALI (high-pitched):
Yes.